[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "And what was he like then?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "he", "like", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Tall and quiet.", "answer_tokens": ["Tall", "and", "quiet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "-- African-American president, an amazing thing?", "question_tokens": ["--", "African-American", "president", ",", "an", "amazing", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Absolutely shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I think both are true.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "both", "are", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "-- you know, it would have been unthinkable that people talked about each other in this way that they are now, quite openly, in Washington?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "would", "have", "been", "unthinkable", "that", "people", "talked", "about", "each", "other", "in", "this", "way", "that", "they", "are", "now", ",", "quite", "openly", ",", "in", "Washington", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No, you're right.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What do you make of this, as a parent and as an American?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", ",", "as", "a", "parent", "and", "as", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "NDERWOOD: Well, you know, I had a conversation with my son when this hit the news.", "answer_tokens": ["NDERWOOD", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "a", "conversation", "with", "my", "son", "when", "this", "hit", "the", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Has it changed?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "changed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I still say -- and, you know, there's a conversation about do you wear -- can you wear a hoodie, should you not wear a hoodie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "say", "--", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "conversation", "about", "do", "you", "wear", "--", "can", "you", "wear", "a", "hoodie", ",", "should", "you", "not", "wear", "a", "hoodie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "But is there a point about a young, black teenager and the hoodie as an emblem of suspicion, of a potential troublemaker?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "there", "a", "point", "about", "a", "young", ",", "black", "teenager", "and", "the", "hoodie", "as", "an", "emblem", "of", "suspicion", ",", "of", "a", "potential", "troublemaker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "The point is, as I said to my son, you're beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "is", ",", "as", "I", "said", "to", "my", "son", ",", "you", "'re", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "You're talking about black-on-black crime?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "talking", "about", "black-on-black", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Did you say 68?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "say", "68", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Sixty-eight.", "answer_tokens": ["Sixty-eight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Are you excited by this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "excited", "by", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Oh, man, Piers, I'm having the time of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "having", "the", "time", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Hmm?", "question_tokens": ["Hmm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Something's missing.", "answer_tokens": ["Something", "'s", "missing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ":", "VBG", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "What is the most corrupting influence, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "most", "corrupting", "influence", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I think the adultery, the paparazzi, everybody cheering and so many -- including many I've worked with -- don't think they deserve such yelling and screaming.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "adultery", ",", "the", "paparazzi", ",", "everybody", "cheering", "and", "so", "many", "--", "including", "many", "I", "'ve", "worked", "with", "--", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "deserve", "such", "yelling", "and", "screaming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How do you feel about being involved in one of the really appalling films ever made?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "involved", "in", "one", "of", "the", "really", "appalling", "films", "ever", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I'm happy I did it for two reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "happy", "I", "did", "it", "for", "two", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "How do you go wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "go", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "He's great.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Eden", "Eden"], "PERSON": ["Garry"]}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "``", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Would you agree that \"Exit to Eden\" was one of the big turkeys?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "that", "``", "Exit", "to", "Eden", "''", "was", "one", "of", "the", "big", "turkeys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, people keep asking me now because I did \"Exit to Eden,\" and they're not trying -- well, Garry, \"Exit to Eden,\" bombed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "people", "keep", "asking", "me", "now", "because", "I", "did", "``", "Exit", "to", "Eden", ",", "''", "and", "they", "'re", "not", "trying", "--", "well", ",", "Garry", ",", "``", "Exit", "to", "Eden", ",", "''", "bombed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Do you think she has it in her to play somebody like Liz Taylor?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "has", "it", "in", "her", "to", "play", "somebody", "like", "Liz", "Taylor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I think she has it in it, if you can get her to come and, you know, on the set and everything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "has", "it", "in", "it", ",", "if", "you", "can", "get", "her", "to", "come", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "on", "the", "set", "and", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Liz Taylor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Julie Andrews"]}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "CD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Who's been the greatest movie star that you've seen for whatever reason?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "been", "the", "greatest", "movie", "star", "that", "you", "'ve", "seen", "for", "whatever", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "The best one I ever worked with just for all the reasons is Julie Andrews.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "one", "I", "ever", "worked", "with", "just", "for", "all", "the", "reasons", "is", "Julie", "Andrews", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "In a dream movie?", "question_tokens": ["In", "a", "dream", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "In a dream movie, I'd put somebody that I have.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "dream", "movie", ",", "I", "'d", "put", "somebody", "that", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "I want you to get lost, all right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "to", "get", "lost", ",", "all", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Hey, nobody moves.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "nobody", "moves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What do you make of what's going on right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "In my country, in my life I saw rough patches.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "country", ",", "in", "my", "life", "I", "saw", "rough", "patches", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "EX", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "What has it done to American society and culture -- the Internet -- do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "it", "done", "to", "American", "society", "and", "culture", "--", "the", "Internet", "--", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", ":", "DT", "NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, first there was gossip, and you have gossip, but every country has gossip.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "there", "was", "gossip", ",", "and", "you", "have", "gossip", ",", "but", "every", "country", "has", "gossip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Are you laughing now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "laughing", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Health care in these days is a bit of a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["Health", "care", "in", "these", "days", "is", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Julia"]}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "You do hint -- just a hint -- an illusion to a romance between Julia Roberts and Richard Gere?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "hint", "--", "just", "a", "hint", "--", "an", "illusion", "to", "a", "romance", "between", "Julia", "Roberts", "and", "Richard", "Gere", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Richard and Julia really had great chemistry, and part of it is because they liked each other, they didn't know each other, and they liked each other, and when they were working, they didn't have anything else to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Richard", "and", "Julia", "really", "had", "great", "chemistry", ",", "and", "part", "of", "it", "is", "because", "they", "liked", "each", "other", ",", "they", "did", "n't", "know", "each", "other", ",", "and", "they", "liked", "each", "other", ",", "and", "when", "they", "were", "working", ",", "they", "did", "n't", "have", "anything", "else", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Julia Roberts", "Richard Gere"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "He was like the coolest dude on TV, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "like", "the", "coolest", "dude", "on", "TV", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Well, he wasn't in real life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "in", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Was he never cool?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "never", "cool", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "ARSHALL: Well, he's cool now.", "answer_tokens": ["ARSHALL", ":", "Well", ",", "he", "'s", "cool", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "He really is, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "really", "is", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Truly.", "answer_tokens": ["Truly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "When did he come into your life, Christian?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "he", "come", "into", "your", "life", ",", "Christian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "He came into my life when I had -- I moved to the beach.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "came", "into", "my", "life", "when", "I", "had", "--", "I", "moved", "to", "the", "beach", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You didn't even notice him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "even", "notice", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I noticed him as a friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "noticed", "him", "as", "a", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "I can take that leap?", "question_tokens": ["I", "can", "take", "that", "leap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "He's a man like I've never met before.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "man", "like", "I", "'ve", "never", "met", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Which is fine if it's you, but how does he feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "fine", "if", "it", "'s", "you", ",", "but", "how", "does", "he", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "I think he -- it's a love/hate thing with my big mouth, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "love/hate", "thing", "with", "my", "big", "mouth", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "There can't be many men who are going to object to having somebody like you, internationally famous, beautiful woman saying it's the best sex she's ever had.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "ca", "n't", "be", "many", "men", "who", "are", "going", "to", "object", "to", "having", "somebody", "like", "you", ",", "internationally", "famous", ",", "beautiful", "woman", "saying", "it", "'s", "the", "best", "sex", "she", "'s", "ever", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "It's not exactly the most damning thing ever, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "exactly", "the", "most", "damning", "thing", "ever", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "What did you learn about yourself on this pretty rocky journey?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "on", "this", "pretty", "rocky", "journey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Well, I mean, to never say never.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "to", "never", "say", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "What's your fighting weight now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "fighting", "weight", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I guess about 135.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "about", "135", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "To any women watching this who have battled this for decades, perhaps, what is the trick to keeping it off?", "question_tokens": ["To", "any", "women", "watching", "this", "who", "have", "battled", "this", "for", "decades", ",", "perhaps", ",", "what", "is", "the", "trick", "to", "keeping", "it", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "Well, you've thrown me the curve ball and now I'm going to hit it out of the park.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'ve", "thrown", "me", "the", "curve", "ball", "and", "now", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "hit", "it", "out", "of", "the", "park", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "How much sex are you having?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "sex", "are", "you", "having", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I'm joking.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "joking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "There's no easy route, is there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "easy", "route", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "There isn't.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Is that the statistic?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "statistic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "I think that is the correct -- I mean, it's a very, very small number.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "is", "the", "correct", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "very", ",", "very", "small", "number", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "There are pictures of you naked in a bathtub?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "pictures", "of", "you", "naked", "in", "a", "bathtub", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Oh, no, there's video.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", ",", "there", "'s", "video", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "It's almost like the classic -- I don't want to say, but it's like the classic ugly duckling story, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "almost", "like", "the", "classic", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "like", "the", "classic", "ugly", "duckling", "story", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Why do you think that at 18, you ended up so overweight, so unhappy, I would guess as well?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "at", "18", ",", "you", "ended", "up", "so", "overweight", ",", "so", "unhappy", ",", "I", "would", "guess", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "It's in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "When you see headlines like that, and millions of people are reading them, what does it do to a woman?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "headlines", "like", "that", ",", "and", "millions", "of", "people", "are", "reading", "them", ",", "what", "does", "it", "do", "to", "a", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "It's unfortunate, but it's -- we are public figures and we put ourselves out there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "unfortunate", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "--", "we", "are", "public", "figures", "and", "we", "put", "ourselves", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "He says here you never wined about being famous?", "question_tokens": ["He", "says", "here", "you", "never", "wined", "about", "being", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "No, I'm sort of an unfamous famous person.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "sort", "of", "an", "unfamous", "famous", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Is that as horrific as it seems?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "as", "horrific", "as", "it", "seems", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "I actually really liked it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "really", "liked", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "You must get all sorts of weirdos, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "get", "all", "sorts", "of", "weirdos", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Well, there's weirdos that you meet in a bar too.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "weirdos", "that", "you", "meet", "in", "a", "bar", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "See, that is true, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["See", ",", "that", "is", "true", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "It's really hard to meet people.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "hard", "to", "meet", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Oh, what, being at a healthy weight or having success?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "what", ",", "being", "at", "a", "healthy", "weight", "or", "having", "success", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "No, appearing on a show like this with your handsome new husband, having the greatest sex of all time.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "appearing", "on", "a", "show", "like", "this", "with", "your", "handsome", "new", "husband", ",", "having", "the", "greatest", "sex", "of", "all", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "When you finished the book and you did the last words and it all went off, what did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "finished", "the", "book", "and", "you", "did", "the", "last", "words", "and", "it", "all", "went", "off", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "AKE: It was an accomplishment.", "answer_tokens": ["AKE", ":", "It", "was", "an", "accomplishment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Of all the things that you talk about in here, the amazing life that you have had up and down, excluding marriage and the birth of children, what has been the greatest and the worst moment of your life, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "things", "that", "you", "talk", "about", "in", "here", ",", "the", "amazing", "life", "that", "you", "have", "had", "up", "and", "down", ",", "excluding", "marriage", "and", "the", "birth", "of", "children", ",", "what", "has", "been", "the", "greatest", "and", "the", "worst", "moment", "of", "your", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "IN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I'd say hitting bottom and losing my house when I was 21 years old, and being 260 pounds and in an abusive relationship, that was my low point and that was also a gift, because I was able to learn a very valuable lesson about money and -- you know, because I had lost a ton of money in that bad choice of buying a house at 19 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "hitting", "bottom", "and", "losing", "my", "house", "when", "I", "was", "21", "years", "old", ",", "and", "being", "260", "pounds", "and", "in", "an", "abusive", "relationship", ",", "that", "was", "my", "low", "point", "and", "that", "was", "also", "a", "gift", ",", "because", "I", "was", "able", "to", "learn", "a", "very", "valuable", "lesson", "about", "money", "and", "--", "you", "know", ",", "because", "I", "had", "lost", "a", "ton", "of", "money", "in", "that", "bad", "choice", "of", "buying", "a", "house", "at", "19", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120427pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 794, "question": "If I could relive a moment right now, what would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "relive", "a", "moment", "right", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "\"Hair Spray.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Hair", "Spray", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]